<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>ResearchExperience on Meng Lu (Ivan) - Resume</title><link>http://example.org/categories/researchexperience/</link><description>Recent content in ResearchExperience on Meng Lu (Ivan) - Resume</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="http://example.org/categories/researchexperience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Research Experience</title><link>http://example.org/posts/research1/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/research1/</guid><description>Natural Language Processing： Propose the novel adversarial attack method FastAttacker, study and design the details of the algorithm. Pre-train BERT model with FEVER datasets Attack BERT model and SOTA Adversarial Attack model—KernelGAT with our framework using FEVER test datasets. Attack target BERT and KernelGAT model compared with two other baselines—TextFooler and BERTAttack. Build models and create adversarial text attacks Doing experiments on algorithms Drafted and edited academic paper content Recommender system： Employ task-oriented optimization procedure and generate personalized bridge function with meta-network.</description></item><item><title>Research Experience</title><link>http://example.org/posts/research2/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/research2/</guid><description> Used unsupervised learning techniques to train a model for cross-section returns analysis, and adopted Latent Dirichlet Allocation model to verify the correctness of the trained model Trained models with supervised learning algorithms &amp;ndash; Decision Trees, SVM, and Neural Networks &amp;ndash; to predict empirical cross-section asset pricing and returns, and provide support for stock selection and investment Applied Natural Language Processing to extract important risk factors from companies’ MD&amp;amp;A disclosures and trained supervised learning model (generalized linear model) to quantify them Constructed 3-factor and 5-factor Fama-French models that help to explain average returns on stocks</description></item><item><title>Research Experience</title><link>http://example.org/posts/research3/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/research3/</guid><description> Trained Neural Networks and SVM models, 2 supervised learning ML algorithms, that can identify the classification of wine from its chemical compositions with accuracy of 96.63% and 98.88% respectively</description></item><item><title>Research Experience</title><link>http://example.org/posts/research4/</link><pubDate>Sat, 01 Jan 2000 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>http://example.org/posts/research4/</guid><description> Devised a simple and efficient sun tracking mechanism using programmable logic controller GE Fanuc PLC Designed 2 different types of sun tracking mechanisms: single axis and dual axis tracking</description></item></channel></rss>